{"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/46328/":{"taskOID":46328,"originalTaskOID":46328,"setID":1013,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1056,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17206,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New gate as part of a new fence","answerDisplayText":"New gate as part of a new fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17207,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New standalone gate","answerDisplayText":"New standalone gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17208,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replacing standalone gate","answerDisplayText":"Replacing standalone gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17209,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Replacing gate as part of existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Replacing gate as part of existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200132,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Gate","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of gate do you want to install?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17210,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway / Estate Gate","answerDisplayText":"Driveway / Estate Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17211,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electric Gate","answerDisplayText":"Electric Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17212,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Security (Non-Driveway) Gate","answerDisplayText":"Security (Non-Driveway) Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17213,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Horse \u0026 Ranch Gate","answerDisplayText":"Horse \u0026 Ranch Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17214,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Industrial Gate","answerDisplayText":"Industrial Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200133,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the material of the gate you would like to install?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7137,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wrought iron","answerDisplayText":"Wrought iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1056,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17206,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New gate as part of a new fence","answerDisplayText":"New gate as part of a new fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17207,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New standalone gate","answerDisplayText":"New standalone gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17208,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replacing standalone gate","answerDisplayText":"Replacing standalone gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17209,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Replacing gate as part of existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Replacing gate as part of existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17206,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New gate as part of a new fence","answerDisplayText":"New gate as part of a new fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17207,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"New standalone gate","answerDisplayText":"New standalone gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17208,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Replacing standalone gate","answerDisplayText":"Replacing standalone gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17209,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Replacing gate as part of existing fence","answerDisplayText":"Replacing gate as part of existing fence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200132,"questionDisplayText":"Purpose of Gate","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of gate do you want to install?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":17210,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway / Estate Gate","answerDisplayText":"Driveway / Estate Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17211,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electric Gate","answerDisplayText":"Electric Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17212,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Security (Non-Driveway) Gate","answerDisplayText":"Security (Non-Driveway) Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17213,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Horse \u0026 Ranch Gate","answerDisplayText":"Horse \u0026 Ranch Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17214,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Industrial Gate","answerDisplayText":"Industrial Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":17210,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Driveway / Estate Gate","answerDisplayText":"Driveway / Estate Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17211,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Electric Gate","answerDisplayText":"Electric Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17212,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Security (Non-Driveway) Gate","answerDisplayText":"Security (Non-Driveway) Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17213,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Horse \u0026 Ranch Gate","answerDisplayText":"Horse \u0026 Ranch Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17214,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Industrial Gate","answerDisplayText":"Industrial Gate","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":200133,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the material of the gate you would like to install?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7137,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wrought iron","answerDisplayText":"Wrought iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7137,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wrought iron","answerDisplayText":"Wrought iron","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6069,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Steel","answerDisplayText":"Steel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":750,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Aluminum","answerDisplayText":"Aluminum","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":7048,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Wood","answerDisplayText":"Wood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":17149,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Security \u0026 Driveway Gate Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/46328/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":46328,"taskName":"Gate for Driveway or Security - Install or Replace","taskDescription":"Install or Replace a Driveway or Security Gate","xmTaskDescriptor":"Security \u0026 Driveway Gate Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":207,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"FENCES building replacement  yard","textMessagingName":"Inst Sec Gate","rolloverLongDesc":null,"rolloverShortDesc":"Usually metal, often automatic-opening gates for security.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace a Driveway or Security Gate.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Home Driveway \u0026 Security Gate Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":30,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Security Gate Install","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Gate for Driveway or Security - Install or Replace","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Security Gate Project","urlName":"Gate-for-Driveway-or-Security-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Driveway Gate Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Security Gate Installation","searchKeywords":"FENCES,building,replacement,,yard,bar,fencing,installer,Security,Gate,Driveway","emcCategoryOid":-12030,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":1013,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}